<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="action_open_about_content_description">About</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_url">https://desperadoboi.github.io/image-to-pdf/privacy/en/</string>
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="action_about_back_content_description">Return to the home screen</string>
    <string name="about_version_format">Version %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_version_unknown">unknown</string>
    <string name="about_description">Create PDFs from images and scan documents without ads.</string>
    <string name="about_device_processing">Files are processed on the device</string>
    <string name="about_no_ads">No ads</string>
    <string name="about_no_registration">No registration</string>
    <string name="action_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_email_developer">Email the developer</string>
    <string name="action_open_privacy_browser">Open policy in browser</string>
    <string name="action_open_local_privacy_content_description">Open the local privacy policy</string>
    <string name="action_email_developer_content_description">Email the developer</string>
    <string name="action_open_privacy_browser_content_description">Open the privacy policy in a browser</string>
    <string name="status_email_app_not_found">No email app was found</string>
    <string name="status_browser_app_not_found">No app was found to open the link. The policy is available inside the app.</string>
    <string name="about_developer_format">Developer: %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_copyright_format">© 2026 %1$s</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_privacy_back_content_description">Return to the About screen</string>
    <string name="privacy_effective_date_label">Effective date</string>
    <string name="privacy_effective_date">July 22, 2026</string>
    <string name="privacy_developer_label">Developer</string>
    <string name="privacy_contact_email_label">Contact email</string>
    <string name="privacy_public_url_label">Public policy URL</string>
    <string name="privacy_scope_title">Scope</string>
    <string name="privacy_scope_body">This policy describes data handling in the ImageToPDF Android application. The current version creates PDF documents from images and scans document pages locally.</string>
    <string name="privacy_handling_title">How data is handled</string>
    <string name="privacy_handling_body">• Images and documents are processed locally on the device.\n• The app does not send images or generated PDF files to the developer’s server.\n• The app does not require registration, create user accounts, display advertising, or use analytics.\n• The app does not sell data or share it with advertisers.\n• The app manifest does not include the INTERNET permission.</string>
    <string name="privacy_access_title">Camera and image access</string>
    <string name="privacy_access_body">CAMERA is used only to capture pages in the document scanning flow. The app accesses images only after the user selects them through a system interface or grants the relevant permission. When MediaStore access is granted, the app reads image information and content locally to display the in-app gallery and process selected pages. If access is denied, available system file selection methods can still be used; the app does not obtain broader access without permission.</string>
    <string name="privacy_storage_title">File storage and deletion</string>
    <string name="privacy_storage_body">Generated PDF files are saved to a location selected by the user through the Android system dialog. After saving, the user controls the file through the selected storage provider or a file manager.\n\nTemporary captures created by the app are kept in app-owned storage for the working session. They are deleted during supported cancellation, retake, page removal, or session cleanup flows. The app does not delete source images selected from the gallery or a third-party document provider.\n\nUsers can remove local app data through Android settings or by uninstalling the app. PDF files saved to a user-selected external location must be deleted by the user.</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_title">Opening and sharing PDF files</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_body">PDF files are opened or shared only after a user action through Android system mechanisms. When sharing, the user selects the recipient application. Any subsequent processing is governed by that recipient’s privacy practices.</string>
    <string name="privacy_changes_title">Policy changes and contact</string>
    <string name="privacy_changes_body">This policy should be reviewed whenever permissions, dependencies, or data handling change. Privacy questions can be sent to the contact email listed above.</string>
</resources>
